

Abenezer Biru

Phone: 0941191054

Address: Addis Ababa, Ethiopia

Email: abenezertesfaye4321@gmail.com

Quick learner with academic abilities and technical knowledge to succeed in different roles. Ready to expand horizons with additional knowledge and abilities gained from training and experience. Always ready to help others and use abilities to support team goals.

EXPERIENCE

School Charity Club

September 2018 - June 2020

Volunteer

- Picked up additional tasks to aid team success.
- Collaborated with team members to achieve target results.
- Developed ongoing programmes using good team communication and collaboration.

Student Council September 2018- May 2019

Member

- Arranging and coordinating events.
- Performing public speech in the class.
- Managing and facilitating methods to resolve students problem.

EDUCATION

Falcon Academy

High School diploma

September 2018 - July 2022

SKILLS

- Problem solving skill
- Communication skill
- Troubleshooting
- Google workspace
- Leadership skill

LANGUAGES

Amharic (Native), English (Fluent)